Our/O national/O monuments/O are/O truly/O spectacular/O and/O “ must/O see/O ” attractions/O when/O visiting/O the/O nation/O ’ s/O capital/O .
Among/O the/O most/O popular/O are/O the/O Washington/LOCATION Monument/LOCATION , the/O Lincoln/ORGANIZATION Memorial/ORGANIZATION , the/O Jefferson/LOCATION Memorial/LOCATION and/O Vietnam/LOCATION Memorial/LOCATION and/O the/O World/O War/O II/O Memorial/O .
See/O a/O guide/O to/O the/O Best/ORGANIZATION Sightseeing/ORGANIZATION Tours/ORGANIZATION in/O Washington/LOCATION DC/LOCATION .
The/O memorials/O are/O beautiful/O at/O night/O when/O they/O are/O illuminated/O .
Many/O of/O them/O are/O open/O 24/O hours/O and/O offer/O great/O views/O of/O the/O city/O .
Arlington/LOCATION National/LOCATION Cemetery/LOCATION , located/O just/O across/O the/O Potomac/LOCATION River/LOCATION , is/O also/O a/O prime/O place/O to/O visit/O and/O home/O to/O dozens/O of/O memorials/O including/O the/O Coast/ORGANIZATION Guard/ORGANIZATION Memorial/ORGANIZATION , the/O Space/O Shuttle/O Challenger/O Memorial/O , Spanish/O - American/O War/O Memorial/O , and/O more/O .
