Jennifer/PERSON Aniston/PERSON and/O Justin/PERSON Theroux/PERSON have/O made/O it/O official/O ! 
The/O couple/O exchanged/O vows/O in/O front/O of/O more/O than/O 70/O family/O members/O and/O friends/O on/O Wednesday/O at/O their/O Bel/LOCATION Air/LOCATION , California/LOCATION , home/O , sources/O confirm/O to/O PEOPLE/ORGANIZATION .
" Guests/O were/O told/O it/O was/O a/O birthday/O party/O for/O Justin/PERSON , " says/O a/O source/O .
" Jen/PERSON and/O Justin/PERSON wanted/O to/O surprise/O guests/O and/O guests/O were/O certainly/O surprised/O .
The/O star/O - studded/O guest/O list/O included/O Friends/NE pals/O Courteney/PERSON Cox/PERSON and/O Lisa/PERSON Kudrow/PERSON , as/O well/O as/O Chelsea/PERSON Handler/PERSON , Howard/PERSON Stern/PERSON and/O Beth/PERSON Ostrosky/PERSON Stern/PERSON , Jason/PERSON Bateman/PERSON , Emily/PERSON Blunt/PERSON and/O John/PERSON Krasinski/PERSON , Sandra/PERSON Bullock/PERSON , Ellen/PERSON DeGeneres/PERSON and/O Portia/PERSON de/PERSON Rossi/PERSON , Will/PERSON Arnett/PERSON , Tobey/PERSON Maguire/PERSON and/O Jennifer/PERSON Meyer/PERSON , Lake/PERSON Bell/PERSON and/O Scott/PERSON Campbell/PERSON , Terry/PERSON Richardson/PERSON , Jimmy/PERSON Kimmel/PERSON , Billy/PERSON Crudup/PERSON , Sia/PERSON , Kathryn/PERSON Hahn/PERSON and/O Whitney/PERSON Cummings/PERSON .
Party/O staffers/O were/O spotted/O bringing/O in/O a/O large/O cake/O topped/O with/O two/O puppet/O characters/O , and/O a/O man/O who/O appeared/O to/O be/O a/O pastor/O was/O seen/O arriving/O on/O the/O grounds/O , according/O to/O TMZ/ORGANIZATION .
Aniston/PERSON , 46/O , and/O Theroux/PERSON , 43/O , got/O engaged/O in/O August/O 2012/O after/O more/O than/O a/O year/O of/O dating/O .
" Justin/PERSON was/O the/O best/O thing/O this/O decade/O , " Aniston/PERSON admits/O about/O her/O 40s/O .
Theroux/PERSON was/O equally/O as/O smitten/O with/O his/O longtime/O love/O , calling/O her/O " gorgeous/O " as/O he/O promoted/O his/O HBO/ORGANIZATION series/O last/O year/O and/O admitting/O that/O their/O approach/O to/O marriage/O involved/O anything/O but/O cold/O feet/O .
" We/O have/O hot/O feet/O , " he/O joked/O .
The/O Friends/NE star/O added/O that/O Theroux/PERSON may/O switch/O up/O his/O own/O chunky/O gold/O ring/O – which/O currently/O spells/O out/O his/O name/O – now/O that/O he/O ' s/O a/O married/O man/O .
" When/O we/O get/O married/O he/O will/O be/O wearing/O his/O ring/O .
It/O just/O won/O ' t/O say/O Justin/PERSON anymore/O , " she/O said/O , adding/O that/O it/O may/O spell/O Jen/PERSON " on/O the/O inside/O " instead/O .
The/O couple/O first/O met/O on/O the/O set/O of/O Tropic/NE Thunder/NE in/O Hawaii/LOCATION in/O 2008/O .
The/O twosome/O , who/O costarred/O in/O 2012/O ' s/O Wanderlust/NE and/O were/O first/O romantically/O linked/O in/O May/O 2011/O , " both/O have/O the/O same/O work/O ethic/O and/O love/O to/O bounce/O ideas/O off/O each/O other/O , " a/O source/O told/O PEOPLE/ORGANIZATION in/O March/O 2014/O .
" Jen/PERSON seems/O more/O confident/O than/O ever/O , and/O they/O ' ve/O become/O a/O great/O team/O .
