Huge/O Game/NE of/NE Thrones/NE news/O : Ian/PERSON McShane/PERSON is/O coming/O to/O Westeros/LOCATION ! The/O Emmy/ORGANIZATION - winning/O British/O actor/O is/O joining/O Thrones/NE season/O 6/O , EW/ORGANIZATION has/O learned/O exclusively/O .
The/O move/O returns/O the/O former/O Deadwood/NE star/O to/O HBO/ORGANIZATION for/O a/O role/O on/O the/O international/O fantasy/O sensation/O .
The/O show/O ’ s/O tight/O - lipped/O production/O will/O not/O reveal/O any/O details/O about/O McShane/PERSON ’ s/O character/O , who/O ’ s/O coming/O on/O board/O for/O the/O most/O mysterious/O season/O yet/O .
Thrones/NE is/O preparing/O to/O dive/O headlong/O into/O narrative/O territory/O not/O yet/O revealed/O in/O author/O George/PERSON R.R./PERSON Martin/PERSON ’ s/O novels/O ( and/O despite/O that/O opening/O sentence/O , McShane/PERSON ’ s/O character/O could/O theoretically/O appear/O in/O Westeros/LOCATION or/O Essos/LOCATION or/O somewhere/O in/O between/O ) .
We/O can/O tell/O you/O , however/O , that/O sources/O say/O McShane/PERSON has/O a/O relatively/O small/O amount/O of/O screen/O - time/O during/O the/O season/O , yet/O his/O character/O is/O of/O key/O importance/O .
McShane/PERSON launched/O to/O American/O TV/O stardom/O by/O playing/O a/O mesmerizingly/O homicidal/O frontier/O kingpin/O Al/PERSON Swearengen/PERSON on/O Deadwood/NE , then/O had/O roles/O in/O films/O Kung/NE Fu/NE Panda/NE , Sexy/NE Beast/NE , Pirates/NE of/NE the/NE Caribbean/NE : On/O Stranger/NE Tides/NE , John/PERSON Wick/PERSON and/O many/O others/O .
His/O most/O recent/O regular/O TV/O gig/O was/O an/O arc/O on/O Showtime/ORGANIZATION ’ s/O Ray/PERSON Donovan/PERSON .
While/O Thrones/NE has/O a/O reputation/O for/O making/O stars/O of/O its/O enormous/O ensemble/O cast/O more/O than/O casting/O already/O widely/O known/O performers/O , McShane/PERSON is/O easily/O one/O of/O the/O most/O recognizable/O actors/O to/O ever/O sign/O on/O with/O the/O series/O .
Plus/O , fans/O of/O his/O work/O — especially/O on/O the/O artfully/O written/O Deadwood/NE — can/O easily/O imagine/O the/O actor/O fitting/O in/O with/O Thrones/NE ’ lawless/O world/O and/O chewing/O on/O the/O show/O ’ s/O Emmy/ORGANIZATION - nominated/O dialogue/O .
Thrones/NE has/O started/O production/O on/O season/O 6/O and/O is/O expected/O to/O return/O for/O 10/O episodes/O next/O spring/O .
Earlier/O this/O week/O , HBO/ORGANIZATION ’ s/O programming/O president/O Michael/PERSON Lombardo/PERSON revealed/O that/O the/O network/O plans/O at/O least/O eight/O seasons/O of/O the/O show/O , a/O bump/O from/O the/O oft/O - reported/O seven/O season/O plan/O .
