At/O a/O press/O conference/O held/O at/O the/O Ritz/LOCATION Carlton/LOCATION hotel/O in/O Herzliya/LOCATION on/O Monday/O night/O , pop/O superstar/O Mariah/PERSON Carey/PERSON discussed/O her/O upcoming/O sell/O - out/O concert/O and/O her/O love/O of/O Israel/LOCATION .
Carey/PERSON , 45/O told/O reporters/O that/O she/O is/O excited/O to/O be/O back/O in/O Israel/LOCATION , adding/O that/O the/O tour/O was/O planned/O during/O her/O visit/O in/O June/O this/O year/O .
The/O singer/O , who/O is/O traveling/O with/O her/O two/O children/O Moroccan/PERSON and/O Monroe/PERSON , spoke/O briefly/O about/O how/O motherhood/O has/O changed/O her/O life/O .
“ I/O would/O say/O it/O ’ s/O the/O best/O thing/O that/O ’ s/O every/O happened/O to/O me/O and/O music/O .
It/O effected/O everything/O , it/O changes/O how/O I/O live/O my/O life/O entirely/O , and/O it/O ’ s/O the/O focus/O of/O who/O I/O am/O entirely/O .
It/O changes/O the/O way/O I/O sleep/O , the/O way/O I/O live/O .
Carey/PERSON ’ s/O Australian/LOCATION billionaire/O boyfriend/O James/PERSON Packer/PERSON accompanied/O her/O .
