TIANJIN/LOCATION , China/LOCATION — This/O bustling/O port/O city/O about/O a/O 90/O - minute/O drive/O from/O the/O Chinese/NE capital/O confronted/O scenes/O of/O death/O and/O devastation/O on/O Thursday/O — huge/O gray/O plumes/O of/O smoke/O , vast/O parking/O lots/O of/O charred/O vehicles/O , blocks/O of/O high/O - rises/O with/O blown/O - out/O windows/O — and/O questions/O about/O what/O had/O caused/O the/O terrifying/O explosions/O at/O a/O warehouse/O storing/O a/O witches/O ’ brew/O of/O toxic/O chemicals/O .
As/O the/O fatalities/O reached/O 50/O from/O the/O blasts/O on/O Wednesday/O night/O , rescue/O workers/O combed/O the/O rubble/O of/O the/O city/O ’ s/O flattened/O warehouse/O district/O for/O bodies/O while/O hundreds/O of/O people/O crowded/O hospitals/O .
At/O least/O 12/O of/O the/O dead/O were/O firefighters/O who/O had/O responded/O to/O earlier/O reports/O of/O a/O blaze/O at/O the/O chemical/O storage/O site/O run/O by/O Ruihai/ORGANIZATION International/ORGANIZATION Logistics/ORGANIZATION , a/O four/O - year/O - old/O company/O that/O unloads/O and/O stores/O hazardous/O cargo/O , the/O state/O news/O media/O and/O government/O officials/O said/O .
On/O Thursday/O afternoon/O , fires/O at/O the/O site/O continued/O to/O produce/O a/O steady/O cloud/O of/O smoke/O after/O Tianjin/LOCATION officials/O , unsure/O about/O the/O nature/O of/O the/O chemicals/O , decided/O to/O let/O the/O blazes/O burn/O out/O on/O their/O own/O .
The/O state/O news/O media/O also/O reported/O that/O a/O military/O team/O of/O specialists/O in/O handling/O chemicals/O had/O been/O sent/O to/O Tianjin/LOCATION .
Residents/O of/O the/O Binhai/LOCATION district/LOCATION , frustrated/O by/O the/O lack/O of/O reliable/O information/O , said/O they/O were/O unsure/O whether/O the/O air/O was/O safe/O , and/O many/O people/O continued/O to/O wear/O disposable/O face/O masks/O throughout/O the/O day/O .
“ Right/O now/O , we/O don/O ’ t/O know/O anything/O , ” said/O Sun/PERSON Meirong/PERSON , 52/O , an/O office/O cleaner/O who/O trudged/O down/O 13/O flights/O of/O stairs/O to/O safety/O with/O her/O 1/O - year/O - old/O grandson/O after/O the/O explosions/O blew/O in/O the/O windows/O and/O front/O door/O of/O her/O apartment/O .
Ruihai/ORGANIZATION ’ s/O website/O was/O inaccessible/O , and/O calls/O to/O the/O company/O were/O met/O with/O a/O busy/O signal/O .
