Google/ORGANIZATION has/O become/O a/O soup/O of/O diverse/O businesses/O — much/O more/O than/O its/O original/O search/O function/O — so/O its/O co/O - founders/O moved/O Monday/O to/O change/O its/O structure/O to/O reflect/O its/O broad/O evolution/O .
The/O Mountain/LOCATION View/LOCATION , Calif./LOCATION , company/O will/O form/O a/O new/O parent/O company/O , called/O Alphabet/ORGANIZATION , that/O will/O be/O run/O by/O Larry/PERSON Page/PERSON , co/O - founder/O and/O current/O CEO/O of/O Google/ORGANIZATION — and/O will/O house/O Google/ORGANIZATION , the/O search/O company/O , as/O well/O as/O Nest/ORGANIZATION , its/O thermostat/O company/O , and/O Calico/ORGANIZATION , a/O unit/O devoted/O to/O age/O and/O longevity/O , Google/ORGANIZATION X/ORGANIZATION and/O YouTube/ORGANIZATION .
Page/PERSON will/O become/O CEO/O of/O Alphabet/ORGANIZATION , with/O co/O - founder/O Sergey/PERSON Brin/PERSON becoming/O Alphabet/ORGANIZATION ’ s/O president/O .
Vice/O Chairman/O Eric/PERSON Schmidt/PERSON will/O likewise/O retain/O his/O title/O for/O Alphabet/ORGANIZATION .
Sundar/PERSON Pichai/PERSON , Google/ORGANIZATION ’ s/O head/O of/O product/O and/O engineering/O for/O online/O businesses/O , will/O become/O CEO/O of/O Google/ORGANIZATION Inc./ORGANIZATION , a/O subsidiary/O that/O will/O include/O the/O search/O engine/O , YouTube/ORGANIZATION , Android/O operating/O system/O and/O Chrome/O browser/O .
Indeed/O , Page/PERSON signaled/O that/O he/O and/O Brin/PERSON are/O looking/O for/O more/O room/O to/O focus/O on/O the/O Google/ORGANIZATION X/O ’ s/O moonshot/O end/O of/O the/O business/O , which/O is/O chasing/O everything/O from/O driverless/O cars/O to/O a/O reversal/O of/O the/O
human/O aging/O process/O .
Ruth/PERSON Porat/PERSON , who/O recently/O joined/O as/O chief/O financial/O officer/O from/O Morgan/ORGANIZATION Stanley/ORGANIZATION , will/O retain/O her/O title/O at/O both/O Alphabet/ORGANIZATION and/O the/O Google/ORGANIZATION subsidiary/O .
Alphabet/ORGANIZATION will/O replace/O Google/ORGANIZATION as/O the/O publicly/O traded/O entity/O and/O all/O shares/O of/O Google/ORGANIZATION will/O automatically/O convert/O into/O the/O same/O number/O of/O shares/O of/O Alphabet/ORGANIZATION .
The/O shares/O will/O continue/O to/O trade/O on/O Nasdaq/ORGANIZATION as/O GOOGL/ORGANIZATION and/O GOOG/ORGANIZATION .
