It/O ' s/O your/O first/O trip/O to/O New/LOCATION York/LOCATION City/LOCATION , and/O you/O ' re/O only/O staying/O for/O a/O three/O - day/O weekend/O .
While/O it/O ' s/O impossible/O to/O take/O in/O all/O the/O excitement/O of/O the/O five/O boroughs/O in/O such/O a/O short/O time/O ( lifelong/O NYC/LOCATION residents/O discover/O something/O new/O every/O day/O ) , you/O can/O still/O enjoy/O many/O of/O the/O City/O ' s/O essential/O attractions/O .
Read/O on/O for/O a/O plan/O that/O will/O help/O you/O make/O the/O most/O of/O your/O time/O — these/O are/O the/O sights/O and/O sounds/O you/O must/O experience/O before/O you/O leave/O .
Day/O One/O ( Midtown/LOCATION ) 
See/O the/O Skyline/O
New/LOCATION York/LOCATION City/LOCATION is/O defined/O by/O its/O skyline/O , and/O all/O city/O skylines/O are/O measured/O against/O New/LOCATION York/LOCATION ' s/O — the/O silhouette/O created/O by/O Manhattan/LOCATION ' s/O buildings/O is/O nothing/O short/O of/O iconic/O .
In/O fact/O , NYC/LOCATION is/O home/O to/O more/O than/O 100/O buildings/O measuring/O 500/O feet/O or/O taller/O .
While/O you/O can/O feel/O this/O immensity/O everywhere/O in/O NYC/LOCATION , it/O ' s/O best/O experienced/O from/O the/O observatories/O at/O the/O Empire/LOCATION State/LOCATION Building/LOCATION and/O at/O Rockefeller/LOCATION Center/LOCATION ' s/O Top/LOCATION of/LOCATION the/LOCATION Rock/LOCATION .
( After/O you/O ' ve/O enjoyed/O the/O scenery/O from/O atop/O a/O skyscraper/O , you/O might/O long/O for/O a/O grounded/O vantage/O point/O that/O gives/O you/O a/O wide/O - angle/O perspective/O on/O Lower/O and/O Midtown/LOCATION Manhattan/LOCATION ; you/O ' ll/O find/O that/O on/O day/O three/O of/O this/O itinerary/O , when/O you/O cross/O the/O Brooklyn/LOCATION Bridge/LOCATION and/O have/O a/O choice/O of/O lookouts/O from/O Brooklyn/LOCATION Bridge/LOCATION Park/LOCATION and/O the/O Brooklyn/LOCATION Heights/LOCATION Promenade/LOCATION .
Walk/O Through/O Times/LOCATION Square/LOCATION
Times/LOCATION Square/LOCATION is/O where/O it/O all/O happens/O .
Twenty/O - four/O hours/O a/O day/O , seven/O days/O a/O week/O , the/O bright/O lights/O , big/O screens/O and/O bustling/O crowds/O perfectly/O embody/O the/O excitement/O of/O the/O city/O that/O never/O sleeps/O .
For/O the/O greatest/O effect/O , visit/O after/O sunset/O — all/O that/O wattage/O will/O make/O you/O think/O it/O ' s/O still/O light/O out/O .
And/O now/O that/O much/O of/O the/O area/O is/O closed/O to/O vehicles/O , you/O can/O safely/O stroll/O in/O the/O streets/O .
While/O there/O , dine/O at/O one/O of/O the/O popular/O eateries/O on/O Restaurant/LOCATION Row/LOCATION ( 46th/LOCATION Street/LOCATION , between/O Eighth/LOCATION and/LOCATION Ninth/LOCATION Avenues/LOCATION ) and/O shop/O in/O the/O huge/O flagship/O stores/O with/O spectacular/O extras/O that/O are/O attractions/O on/O their/O own/O ( Toys/ORGANIZATION " R/ORGANIZATION " Us/ORGANIZATION , for/O example/O , has/O an/O indoor/O Ferris/O wheel/O .
Still/O daylight/O ? From/O Times/LOCATION Square/LOCATION , it/O ' s/O just/O a/O 15/O - minute/O stroll/O — heading/O north/O on/O Sixth/LOCATION Avenue/LOCATION , past/O classic/O sights/O like/O Rockefeller/LOCATION Center/LOCATION and/O Radio/LOCATION City/LOCATION Music/LOCATION Hall/LOCATION — to/O the/O Museum/LOCATION of/LOCATION Modern/LOCATION Art/LOCATION ( MoMA/LOCATION ) , where/O you/O can/O visit/O one/O of/O the/O world/O ' s/O finest/O collections/O of/O contemporary/O art/O .
Give/O Your/O Regards/O to/O Broadway/LOCATION
Nobody/O does/O live/O theater/O like/O NYC/LOCATION .
Whether/O you/O ' re/O into/O dramas/O , comedies/O or/O musicals/O , you/O ' ll/O find/O them/O all/O in/O the/O City/O ' s/O Theatre/LOCATION District/LOCATION , where/O Broadway/LOCATION shows/O burst/O with/O eye/O - popping/O sets/O , A/O - list/O celebrities/O and/O , above/O all/O , pizzazz/O .
You/O can/O choose/O from/O long/O - running/O shows/O like/O Chicago/LOCATION and/O Mamma/NE Mia/NE ! , newer/O smash/O musicals/O such/O as/O Kinky/NE Boots/NE and/O The/O Book/NE of/NE Mormon/NE and/O projects/O featuring/O film/O stars/O like/O Matthew/PERSON Broderick/PERSON , Helen/PERSON Mirren/PERSON and/O Jake/PERSON Gyllenhal/PERSON in/O stage/O roles/O .
All/O of/O the/O performances/O demonstrate/O why/O this/O famed/O NYC/LOCATION thoroughfare/O has/O become/O synonymous/O with/O theater/O itself/O .
Visit/O the/O TKTS/ORGANIZATION Discount/O Booth/O in/O Times/LOCATION Square/LOCATION for/O discounted/O tickets/O to/O some/O shows/O , and/O climb/O the/O red/O steps/O for/O an/O unmatched/O view/O of/O the/O area/O .
